# Eli Pandolfo

Software Developer

### **Personal Info**

#### Email

elipandolfo@gmail.com

#### Phone

• (802) 498-8164

#### Github

• github.com/elip12

#### Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/eli-pandolfo
Website

#### Website

elip12.github.io

### **Professional Skills**

### **Development Practices**

- · CI/CD
- Agile
- TDD/BDD
- RESTful API Architecture
- Relational Database Design
- · Software Testing

### Languages

- Go
- Python
- Bash
- JavaScript & HTML
- SQL
- C & C++
- Java

### Tools

- UNIX/Linux
- Kubernetes
- Saltstack
- AWS
- Terraform
- Postgres
- Django
- Vue

# **Certifications**

· AWS Technical Professional

### **About Me**

Software engineer at Robinhood recently graduated from UC Santa Cruz with advanced programming experience and coursework in math and biology. Intent on bridging the gap between development, especially around open-source orchestration tools, and operations, including debugging, linux systems, and networking. In my down time I bike, surf, play jazz sax, and am an avid backpacker and skier. Ready to learn and contribute in any way possible.

## **Experience**

### Infrastructure Engineer Robinhood, Menlo Park, CA 2020 - present

- Implemented autoscaling policies saving the company 50K/month in infrastructure costs
- Strengthen infrastructure quality & reliability, promote anti-fragility, and enhance developer productivity by extending Kubernetes APIs and reducing dependency on Terraform & Salt.
- Lessen frequency and impact of sevs by identifying and eliminating P0 risks, with the goal of carrying Robinhood's systems to 99.999% reliability.

### Lab Programmer LEEPS Lab, UC Santa Cruz, CA 2017 - 2018, 2019 - 2020

- Developed real-time multiplayer economics experiments for research into markets, game theory, and decision-making.
- · Wrote Python and Bash scripts to analyze and visualize experiment data.
- · Set up and maintained a public Linux production server.
- · Hired, trained, and supervised four lab programmers.

### Software Engineering Intern productOps, Santa Cruz, CA 2018 - 2019

- Developed Node API and Postgres database that simplifies and streamlines the creation of AWS infrastructure, reducing startup overhead for new projects.
- Wrote end-to-end and integration tests for Angular/Node web apps, ensuring safe updates to production applications with 1000+ users.

## **Education**

### BS Computer Science UC Santa Cruz 2016 - 2020

- · GPA: 3.96
- Regent's Scholarship
- · College Scholars Program
- Undergraduate bioinformatics & machine learning research with <u>Lings</u> Lab
- Areas of focus: bioinformatics, computational economics, data wrangling & machine learning, parallel processing

### 42 Piscine 42 Silicon Valley 2017

· Four-week intensive C coding program at School 42 in Fremont, CA

# **Projects**

### Genome Wide Association Study Lings Lab, UC Santa Cruz

- Microbial GWAS program that uses statistical relational learning to predict genetic causes of bacterial phenotypes.
- Successfully identified genes in *E. coli* known to cause antibiotic resistance, outperforming a state-of-the-art method.

### Computational Economics Experiment LEEPS Lab, UC Santa Cruz

- Multiplayer web app with Vue.js UI simulating people waiting in a queue.
- Players trade places with each other for money in real time.

### StenoScribe Android App Mobile Apps Class, UC Santa Cruz

 Mobile app for streamlining note-taking during meetings. Users can instantly share speech-to-text transcriptions, photos, and documents.